<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: cycling | ]]></title>
  <link href="/categories/cycling/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="/"/>
  <updated>2014-01-09T13:41:41+00:00</updated>
  <id>/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="https://github.com/recurser/jekyll-plugins">Recurser</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Grim Reaper]]></title>
    <link href="/cycling/2011/12/05/the-grim-reaper/"/>
    <updated>2011-12-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>/cycling/2011/12/05/the-grim-reaper</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This makes pretty grim reading - Every death on every road in Great Britain 1999-2010.</p>

<p>It would seem if you’re a cyclist and you want to stay alive then you should avoid riding during the Monday to Friday rush hours and not bother heading out on a Saturday or Sunday afternoon.</p>

<p>Strangely, looking at the map of bike casualties in the Glasgow area, most of them seem to occur in fine weather during daylight. There also seems to be a disproportionate number of old men (60+) involved.</p>

<p>If the map is accurate and to be believed it looks like one guy died while cycling along the M74.</p>

<p>Thankfully though, the general trend for the number of cyclists being killed on the roads between 1999 - 2010 seems to heading downwards. This has got to be a good thing considering the number of cyclists on the road during that time has most definitely been on the rise.</p>

<p>Don’t let the doom mongers put you off and get out and ride!</p>]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bealach Mor]]></title>
    <link href="/cycling/2011/12/01/bealach-mor/"/>
    <updated>2011-12-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>/cycling/2011/12/01/bealach-mor</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Just signed up for the Bealach Mor (140km, 3000m ascent) and the Ullapool Sportive. Help ma’ boab!!!</p>

<p>Two more sportives to add to the ever growing list along with the New Forest Spring Sportive, Etape Caledonia, the Wight Ferry Sportive and the Glasgow 100.</p>

<p>It’s going to be a busy 2012!!!</p>

<p>Full details on the cycleography calendar here - <a href="http://www.cycleography.com/calendar-2/">http://www.cycleography.com/calendar-2/</a></p>]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>