<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: blog | ]]></title>
  <link href="/categories/blog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="/"/>
  <updated>2014-01-07T02:22:41+00:00</updated>
  <id>/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="https://github.com/recurser/jekyll-plugins">Recurser</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who are you?]]></title>
    <link href="/blog/2012/01/26/who-are-you/"/>
    <updated>2012-01-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>/blog/2012/01/26/who-are-you</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I woke up in a social network, the internet policeman knew my name</p>

<p>Google now let’s you peruse the various bits of demographic information they store about you so they can try and sell you stuff.</p>

<p>Google says:</p>

<blockquote>
<p>Many websites, such as news sites and blogs, partner with us to show ads to their visitors. To see ads that are more related to you and your interests, edit the categories below, which are based on sites you have recently visited. Your interests are associated with an advertising cookie that’s stored in your browser.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>So who does google think you are? You can find out here - <a href="https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb">https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb</a></p>

<p>This is who google thinks I am</p>

<blockquote>
<p>Your categories Below you can review the interests and inferred demographics that Google has associated with your cookie.</p>

<ul>
<li>Arts &amp; Entertainment</li>

<li>Arts &amp; Entertainment - Music &amp; Audio</li>

<li>Arts &amp; Entertainment - Music &amp; Audio - Rock Music</li>

<li>Computers &amp; Electronics - Programming</li>

<li>Games - Computer &amp; Video Games - Simulation Games</li>

<li>Internet &amp; Telecom - Web Services - Web Hosting &amp; Domain Registration</li>

<li>News - Weather</li>

<li>Sports - Individual Sports - Cycling</li>

<li>World Localities - Europe - Western Europe - United Kingdom</li>

<li>World Localities - Europe - Western Europe - United Kingdom - Scotland</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
<p>Your demographics We infer your age and gender based on the websites you’ve visited.</p>

<ul>
<li>Age: 35-44</li>

<li>Gender: Male</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>

<p>Scary that it’s pretty much spot on? Or sad that I’m so predictable?</p>

<p>You can go sleep at home tonight, If you can log off and walk away</p>]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The return of the net]]></title>
    <link href="/website/blog/2011/11/30/return-of-the-net/"/>
    <updated>2011-11-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>/website/blog/2011/11/30/return-of-the-net</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Well after a couple of years hiatus I’ve finally got round to putting something back up at netclectic.com. I’m not sure where it’s going to go just yet but I’m working on it, hopefully it will evolve in to something resembling a website in the coming months.</p>

<p>It feels good to be back :-)</p>]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>